<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="1A1A0C49-49E9-40B5-9888-231FAF881652">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121125" date="2012-11-25 20:54:17 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>EUGENE &#x2014; He probably didn't realize it, but 8-year-old Cole Hexum was lifting the Ducks' spirits Monday morning, maybe even more than they were lifting his.&#xD;&#xD;Coming off a shocking overtime loss to Stanford just 36 hours earlier, the Ducks returned to the practice field feeling a little down, a little disappointed.&#xD;&#xD;Standing on the sideline inside the Moshofsky Center, Oregon's practice facility, Cole got a rare outsider's glimpse at the Ducks at work. Cole was there wearing what has become one of his most prized possessions: a bright yellow "89" Oregon beanie that he refuses to remove from his small, bald head.&#xD;&#xD;Cole was, according to his father, in awe as one by one Oregon players approached him during practice.&#xD;&#xD;Eric Dungy shook Cole's hand as he introduced himself. "We're pulling for you," Dungy said.&#xD;&#xD;Terrance Mitchell made a play near the sideline and then gave Cole an emphatic high-five. Bryan Bennett did the same after scrambling out of bounds.&#xD;&#xD;Coach Chip Kelly then came over and chatted with Cole and his family for at least five minutes.&#xD;&#xD;"I couldn't even name all the players that stopped by," Cole's father, Brian Hexum, said Tuesday. "For them to do that in the middle of practice ... it was really special."&#xD;&#xD;It was a special sight, too, for Oregon senior receiver Will Murphy, who made the connection happen. And, in doing so, made his teammates' day a little brighter.&#xD;&#xD;"It definitely puts everything into perspective," Murphy said. "We were a little beat up and upset about the loss, but then you see him &#x2014; this happy, little 8-year-old going through something none of us could even imagine."&#xD;&#xD;&lt;b&gt;No fear&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;Cole was diagnosed with Stage IV Burkitt's leukemia on Sept. 13, just 12 days after he attended, with his father, the Oregon season opener against Arkansas State, and just nine days before his eighth birthday.&#xD;The outlook is optimistic for Cole, who has undergone five rounds of chemotherapy treatment. He was to spend Thanksgiving at the Hexum's Bethany home with his dad, mom, Michelle, and two brothers, Tyler, 17, and Cade, 4.&#xD;It's a rare day away from Randall Children's Hospital at Legacy Emanuel, where Cole has spent much of his time the past 2-1/2 months. He'll be back to the hospital Monday for more treatment.&#xD;"He's gone through the majority of really hard stuff," Brian Hexum said.&#xD;Burkitt's is a rare and aggressive type of leukemia that requires aggressive treatment. In Cole's case, he had 90 percent of his bone marrow affected by the diseased white blood cells.&#xD;"They were just blasting him with the highest dosage (of chemotherapy) you can," Brian Hexum said. "It's absolutely brutal."&#xD;Sores in his mouth made eating impossible for awhile; he had to be fed through a tube.&#xD;The family absorbed another shock on Nov. 9 when Brian's father, Richard Hexum &#x2014; "Grampy Hexum" to the boys &#x2014; died of pulmonary fibrosis in Eugene. He was 70. "He and Cole really bonded," Brian Hexum said. "I wish Grampy would've been around to see Cole get through this."&#xD;Cole hasn't been able to attend school, much less play the sports he loves &#x2014; soccer, flag football and basketball.&#xD;&#xD;Cole Hexum holds the championship trophy from the "Cole's Bros."&#xD;&lt;i&gt;Courtesy Hexum family&#xD;&lt;/i&gt;Instead, Cole's flag football team, previously the Destroyers, changed its team name to "Cole's Bros." Cole wasn't able to attend any of the games, but the second-graders wore messages of support for their teammate on their eye black, and then went undefeated to win their league championship. Cole got his own honorary trophy.&#xD;Brian Hexum, an Oregon graduate and a season-ticket holder for the Ducks since 1994, has long enjoyed taking Cole to sporting events. Cole will sit patiently and intently at games, especially when watching the Ducks.&#xD;"He doesn't get fidgety or anything," Brian said. "He really understands what's going on."&#xD;When he was diagnosed in September, Cole also wanted to understand what was happening to him. Someone asked him if he was afraid.&#xD;"No," Cole said. "I saw my mom go through it. I can handle it, too."&#xD;Michelle Hexum was diagnosed with ovarian cancer on Feb. 5, 2009. Her successful fight inspired Cole, whose final treatment is scheduled for Feb. 4, 2013.&#xD;"If Cole wasn't so strong, it would make it harder for us to handle," Brian said.&#xD;The &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://blog.oregonlive.com/runoregon/2012/11/run_for_cole_race_recap.html"&gt;unexpected outpouring of support&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &#x2014; from family, friends and total strangers &#x2014; has made things easier for the Hexums, too. Fundraisers, donations and sales of "Go Team Cole" gear &#x2014; available at the family's website, &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://goteamcole.com/"&gt;GoTeamCole.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &#x2014; is covering much of the estimated $500,000 in medical expenses.&#xD;After Cole gets better, the Hexums are planning to support other sick children through additional fundraising. They've already provided gifts and encouragement for families going through a similar ordeal.&#xD;"We've been really blessed," Brian said. "It really restores your faith in humanity."&#xD;&lt;b&gt;A special connection&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;Will Murphy first heard about Cole's illness through his brother, Andrew, who works with a family friend of the Hexums. Soon, Murphy was posting messages of support on the Go Team Cole Facebook page, sending a Ducks poster autographed by virtually the entire team and shipping off that "89" beanie &#x2014; Murphy's uniform number &#x2014; that Cole now refuses to take off.&#xD;In return, Murphy got a yellow "Team Cole" bracelet and a new friendship.&#xD;When Murphy, a senior from Albany, scored his first UO touchdown in the Ducks' victory over Cal two weeks ago, the Hexums paused the TV while Murphy, laying on his back, held the football in the air, the yellow bracelet around his left wrist; Cole stood in front of the TV to pose for a picture.&#xD;"I thought of Cole right away," Murphy said of his touchdown.&#xD;Murphy had extended an invitation to the Hexums to visit an Oregon practice; the plan was for Cole and the family to attend the Washington game last month, but Cole wasn't well enough to travel yet. Murphy sent a message after the game: "This win was for you, Cole."&#xD;Finally, doctors cleared Cole to travel to Eugene last week for the Stanford game. The day started with an unknown UO student volunteering to hold up a giant-sized sign of Cole's face in the background of ESPN's "College GameDay" show, which was being broadcast from the UO campus.&#xD;On Monday, Cole got to meet his favorite Duck.&#xD;"I was pretty pumped we finally made it happen," Murphy said.&#xD;As they left practice Monday morning, Cole riding on top of his dad's shoulders, Murphy walking and chatting next to them, it was hard to tell who enjoyed the experience more.&#xD;-- &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:ajude@oregonian.com"&gt;Adam Jude&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;; follow on &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/A_Jude"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="22_An_uplifting_visit_with_the_Oregon_Ducks_for_young_Cole_Hexum_-_and_vice_versa_files/shapeimage_3.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="327px" height="300px"/>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Thursday, November 22, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>An uplifting visit with the Oregon Ducks for young Cole Hexum -- and vice versa</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
