<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="1A1A0C49-49E9-40B5-9888-231FAF881652">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20121125" date="2012-11-26 00:54:24 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;a href="http://democratherald.com/search/?l=50&amp;sd=desc&amp;s=start_time&amp;f=html&amp;byline=By%20JESSE%20SOWA%2C%20Albany%20Democrat-Herald"&gt;By JESSE SOWA, Albany Democrat-Herald&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xD;EUGENE &#x2014; As he prepares for Saturday&#x2019;s Civil War game, Will Murphy will be wearing a rubber wristband with the phrase &#x201C;TEAMCOLE.&#x201D;&#xD;That wristband gives the Oregon senior wide receiver a constant reminder of the struggles his new friend is going through.&#xD;In the back of Murphy&#x2019;s mind will be Cole Hexum, an 8-year-old Portland boy with stage four Burkitt&#x2019;s leukemia, a rare and highly aggressive cancer.&#xD;While other kids his age are going to school and enjoying playing sports, Cole has spent hundreds of hours the past few months in the Randall Children&#x2019;s Hospital at Legacy Emanuel in northeast Portland.&#xD;He was diagnosed with Burkitt&#x2019;s on Sept. 13, nine days short of his eighth birthday.&#xD;Murphy, a West Albany High grad, learned about Cole through Murphy&#x2019;s brother, Andrew, who works with a friend of the Hexum family.&#xD;Murphy and the Oregon football program rallied around Cole, sending him team-issued cleats, game gloves and wristbands, among other items.&#xD;Cole wears his yellow Ducks skull cap with Murphy&#x2019;s No. 89 everywhere he goes.&#xD;Cole is a soccer player but he loves his Ducks.&#xD;Monday, Cole got to meet Murphy, his favorite Oregon player, in person for the first time as Cole and his parents, Brian and Michelle, got an invitation to Oregon&#x2019;s closed practice.&#xD;&#x201C;It was pretty fun to see that big smile on his face,&#x201D; Murphy said.&#xD;Cole also got to meet the entire team, including coach Chip Kelly, who spent several minutes during practice talking with the family.&#xD;Murphy later gave the family a tour of Oregon&#x2019;s top-notch treatment and training facilities.&#xD;&#x201C;He&#x2019;s going to go home and talk to his friends about it, and I&#x2019;m sure he&#x2019;s going to remember this forever,&#x201D; Michelle Hexum said.&#xD;Cole and Brian, an Oregon graduate and season-ticket holder, attended last week&#x2019;s Oregon-Stanford game, the first one Cole had been cleared by doctors to attend.&#xD;The family has been given tickets to this Saturday&#x2019;s game by Oregon and will head to Corvallis if Cole is feeling well enough.&#xD;It&#x2019;s been a long 10 weeks for the Hexums.&#xD;Cole has spent roughly 80 percent of that time in the hospital, enduring five rounds of chemotherapy that have resulted in losing his hair, painful mouth sores, weight loss and eating through a feeding tube.&#xD;&#x201C;He&#x2019;s just this old soul and he takes it all in,&#x201D; Michelle Hexum said. &#x201C;He&#x2019;s a champion about it. He never once has had a bad attitude about it.&#x201D;&#xD;Cole&#x2019;s diagnosis had to seem like a bad dream for the family.&#xD;Michelle learned she had ovarian cancer in 2009.&#xD;Like her son, she lost her hair during chemotherapy, which helped rid her body of the cancer for good.&#xD;The frightening experience has helped Cole to not be afraid of his own illness.&#xD;&#x201C;It&#x2019;s pretty powerful stuff,&#x201D; Brian said.&#xD;Murphy and Oregon offensive coordinator Mark Helfrich had both heard about Cole&#x2019;s recent diagnosis and were spreading the word to the team.&#xD;Jeff Lockie, a freshman quarterback, sent Cole an email. After Monday&#x2019;s practice, Lockie brought Cole some more wristbands and other items.&#xD;&#x201C;He&#x2019;s been dealing with something harder than anybody else is,&#x201D; Lockie said, calling it a &#x201C;no-brainer&#x201D; to step forward and be involved. &#x201C;Being able to branch out and help out in the community has been one of the coolest parts of going to school here.&#x201D;&#xD;Numerous children with illnesses have visited the Ducks in recent years through the Make-A-Wish Foundation.&#xD;Murphy learned quickly the impact he can have with just a small gesture.&#xD;&#x201C;It really doesn&#x2019;t take a whole lot to make somebody else&#x2019;s day,&#x201D; he said.&#xD;The middle child of three boys, Cole got showered with items from the Ducks and beyond.&#xD;The Portland Winterhawks reached out, inviting Cole and his family to watch a game from a suite. Cole got a visit from Blaze, the Portland Trail Blazers&#x2019; mascot, who came with a bevy of gifts that included an autographed jersey from LaMarcus Aldridge.&#xD;Medical expenses have piled up on the Hexums. Their bills are nearing $500,000 with three months of chemotherapy and more hospital stays still to come.&#xD;Ten friends of the family formed Team Cole to raise money through various means and to also provide meals and services for the family.&#xD;A Facebook page and website (goteamcole.com) were created to provide updates on Cole and solicit help.&#xD;The support &#x2014; both emotional and financial &#x2014; has been overwhelming to the family.&#xD;Fundraisers during the last two months have included a fun run and soccer tournament. Several Portland-area restaurants have made donations.&#xD;Cole&#x2019;s story has been presented by at least two Portland television stations.&#xD;His fight against cancer also got some national attention when his face &#x2014; skull cap and all &#x2014; along with the website address appeared on a large sign during last Saturday morning&#x2019;s ESPN College GameDay show broadcast from the Oregon campus.&#xD;Hospital stays have limited Cole&#x2019;s time with his family and friends.&#xD;Trips home have often been short due to uncontrollable fevers and pain.&#xD;He&#x2019;s done his best to keep up on his schoolwork, but sometimes he&#x2019;s just too sick to try.&#xD;The chemotherapy is working and doctors see a light at the end of the proverbial tunnel.&#xD;If all goes well, Cole will be free of cancer in just a few months.&#xD;The plan is to have him back in school at Jacob Wismer Elementary and out on the soccer field by the end of spring break.&#xD;&#x201C;His prognosis is excellent after that,&#x201D; Brian Hexum said. &#x201C;He&#x2019;s had a little detour or two but he&#x2019;s handling it like a champ.&#x201D;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="22_Civil_War_football__Murphy_takes_field_as_part_of_TEAMCOLE_files/shapeimage_3.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="403px" height="304px"/>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Thursday, November 22, 2012&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Civil War football: Murphy takes field as part of 'TEAMCOLE'</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
