<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>TeamCole.org Blog</title>
    <link>http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description>This blog encompasses all of the news stories for Cole.&lt;br/&gt;If you would like to read about the daily updates for Cole, please follow the Team Cole FaceBook group here:&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Blog_files/ColeBri.jpg</url>
      <title>TeamCole.org Blog</title>
      <link>http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Civil War football: Murphy takes field as part of 'TEAMCOLE'</title>
      <link>http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Entries/2012/11/22_Civil_War_football__Murphy_takes_field_as_part_of_TEAMCOLE.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">940c498a-4786-461a-8a90-d9040453c4f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 16:48:48 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Entries/2012/11/22_Civil_War_football__Murphy_takes_field_as_part_of_TEAMCOLE_files/50adbac215759.preview-620.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Media/object001_1.png&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:160px; height:121px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://democratherald.com/search/?l=50&amp;sd=desc&amp;s=start_time&amp;f=html&amp;byline=By%20JESSE%20SOWA%2C%20Albany%20Democrat-Herald&quot;&gt;By JESSE SOWA, Albany Democrat-Herald&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;EUGENE — As he prepares for Saturday’s Civil War game, Will Murphy will be wearing a rubber wristband with the phrase “TEAMCOLE.”&lt;br/&gt;That wristband gives the Oregon senior wide receiver a constant reminder of the struggles his new friend is going through.&lt;br/&gt;In the back of Murphy’s mind will be Cole Hexum, an 8-year-old Portland boy with stage four Burkitt’s leukemia, a rare and highly aggressive cancer.&lt;br/&gt;While other kids his age are going to school and enjoying playing sports, Cole has spent hundreds of hours the past few months in the Randall Children’s Hospital at Legacy Emanuel in northeast Portland.&lt;br/&gt;He was diagnosed with Burkitt’s on Sept. 13, nine days short of his eighth birthday.&lt;br/&gt;Murphy, a West Albany High grad, learned about Cole through Murphy’s brother, Andrew, who works with a friend of the Hexum family.&lt;br/&gt;Murphy and the Oregon football program rallied around Cole, sending him team-issued cleats, game gloves and wristbands, among other items.&lt;br/&gt;Cole wears his yellow Ducks skull cap with Murphy’s No. 89 everywhere he goes.&lt;br/&gt;Cole is a soccer player but he loves his Ducks.&lt;br/&gt;Monday, Cole got to meet Murphy, his favorite Oregon player, in person for the first time as Cole and his parents, Brian and Michelle, got an invitation to Oregon’s closed practice.&lt;br/&gt;“It was pretty fun to see that big smile on his face,” Murphy said.&lt;br/&gt;Cole also got to meet the entire team, including coach Chip Kelly, who spent several minutes during practice talking with the family.&lt;br/&gt;Murphy later gave the family a tour of Oregon’s top-notch treatment and training facilities.&lt;br/&gt;“He’s going to go home and talk to his friends about it, and I’m sure he’s going to remember this forever,” Michelle Hexum said.&lt;br/&gt;Cole and Brian, an Oregon graduate and season-ticket holder, attended last week’s Oregon-Stanford game, the first one Cole had been cleared by doctors to attend.&lt;br/&gt;The family has been given tickets to this Saturday’s game by Oregon and will head to Corvallis if Cole is feeling well enough.&lt;br/&gt;It’s been a long 10 weeks for the Hexums.&lt;br/&gt;Cole has spent roughly 80 percent of that time in the hospital, enduring five rounds of chemotherapy that have resulted in losing his hair, painful mouth sores, weight loss and eating through a feeding tube.&lt;br/&gt;“He’s just this old soul and he takes it all in,” Michelle Hexum said. “He’s a champion about it. He never once has had a bad attitude about it.”&lt;br/&gt;Cole’s diagnosis had to seem like a bad dream for the family.&lt;br/&gt;Michelle learned she had ovarian cancer in 2009.&lt;br/&gt;Like her son, she lost her hair during chemotherapy, which helped rid her body of the cancer for good.&lt;br/&gt;The frightening experience has helped Cole to not be afraid of his own illness.&lt;br/&gt;“It’s pretty powerful stuff,” Brian said.&lt;br/&gt;Murphy and Oregon offensive coordinator Mark Helfrich had both heard about Cole’s recent diagnosis and were spreading the word to the team.&lt;br/&gt;Jeff Lockie, a freshman quarterback, sent Cole an email. After Monday’s practice, Lockie brought Cole some more wristbands and other items.&lt;br/&gt;“He’s been dealing with something harder than anybody else is,” Lockie said, calling it a “no-brainer” to step forward and be involved. “Being able to branch out and help out in the community has been one of the coolest parts of going to school here.”&lt;br/&gt;Numerous children with illnesses have visited the Ducks in recent years through the Make-A-Wish Foundation.&lt;br/&gt;Murphy learned quickly the impact he can have with just a small gesture.&lt;br/&gt;“It really doesn’t take a whole lot to make somebody else’s day,” he said.&lt;br/&gt;The middle child of three boys, Cole got showered with items from the Ducks and beyond.&lt;br/&gt;The Portland Winterhawks reached out, inviting Cole and his family to watch a game from a suite. Cole got a visit from Blaze, the Portland Trail Blazers’ mascot, who came with a bevy of gifts that included an autographed jersey from LaMarcus Aldridge.&lt;br/&gt;Medical expenses have piled up on the Hexums. Their bills are nearing $500,000 with three months of chemotherapy and more hospital stays still to come.&lt;br/&gt;Ten friends of the family formed Team Cole to raise money through various means and to also provide meals and services for the family.&lt;br/&gt;A Facebook page and website (goteamcole.com) were created to provide updates on Cole and solicit help.&lt;br/&gt;The support — both emotional and financial — has been overwhelming to the family.&lt;br/&gt;Fundraisers during the last two months have included a fun run and soccer tournament. Several Portland-area restaurants have made donations.&lt;br/&gt;Cole’s story has been presented by at least two Portland television stations.&lt;br/&gt;His fight against cancer also got some national attention when his face — skull cap and all — along with the website address appeared on a large sign during last Saturday morning’s ESPN College GameDay show broadcast from the Oregon campus.&lt;br/&gt;Hospital stays have limited Cole’s time with his family and friends.&lt;br/&gt;Trips home have often been short due to uncontrollable fevers and pain.&lt;br/&gt;He’s done his best to keep up on his schoolwork, but sometimes he’s just too sick to try.&lt;br/&gt;The chemotherapy is working and doctors see a light at the end of the proverbial tunnel.&lt;br/&gt;If all goes well, Cole will be free of cancer in just a few months.&lt;br/&gt;The plan is to have him back in school at Jacob Wismer Elementary and out on the soccer field by the end of spring break.&lt;br/&gt;“His prognosis is excellent after that,” Brian Hexum said. “He’s had a little detour or two but he’s handling it like a champ.”</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Entries/2012/11/22_Civil_War_football__Murphy_takes_field_as_part_of_TEAMCOLE_files/50adbac215759.preview-620.jpg" length="105835" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An uplifting visit with the Oregon Ducks for young Cole Hexum -- and vice versa</title>
      <link>http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Entries/2012/11/22_An_uplifting_visit_with_the_Oregon_Ducks_for_young_Cole_Hexum_-_and_vice_versa.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f430d85-5a53-4fc1-a409-541e43eedb7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2012 09:47:56 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Entries/2012/11/22_An_uplifting_visit_with_the_Oregon_Ducks_for_young_Cole_Hexum_-_and_vice_versa_files/11901891-large.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Media/object010_1.png&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:160px; height:147px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;EUGENE — He probably didn't realize it, but 8-year-old Cole Hexum was lifting the Ducks' spirits Monday morning, maybe even more than they were lifting his.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Coming off a shocking overtime loss to Stanford just 36 hours earlier, the Ducks returned to the practice field feeling a little down, a little disappointed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Standing on the sideline inside the Moshofsky Center, Oregon's practice facility, Cole got a rare outsider's glimpse at the Ducks at work. Cole was there wearing what has become one of his most prized possessions: a bright yellow &amp;quot;89&amp;quot; Oregon beanie that he refuses to remove from his small, bald head.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Cole was, according to his father, in awe as one by one Oregon players approached him during practice.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Eric Dungy shook Cole's hand as he introduced himself. &amp;quot;We're pulling for you,&amp;quot; Dungy said.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Terrance Mitchell made a play near the sideline and then gave Cole an emphatic high-five. Bryan Bennett did the same after scrambling out of bounds.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Coach Chip Kelly then came over and chatted with Cole and his family for at least five minutes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;I couldn't even name all the players that stopped by,&amp;quot; Cole's father, Brian Hexum, said Tuesday. &amp;quot;For them to do that in the middle of practice ... it was really special.&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It was a special sight, too, for Oregon senior receiver Will Murphy, who made the connection happen. And, in doing so, made his teammates' day a little brighter.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;It definitely puts everything into perspective,&amp;quot; Murphy said. &amp;quot;We were a little beat up and upset about the loss, but then you see him — this happy, little 8-year-old going through something none of us could even imagine.&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;No fear&lt;br/&gt;Cole was diagnosed with Stage IV Burkitt's leukemia on Sept. 13, just 12 days after he attended, with his father, the Oregon season opener against Arkansas State, and just nine days before his eighth birthday.&lt;br/&gt;The outlook is optimistic for Cole, who has undergone five rounds of chemotherapy treatment. He was to spend Thanksgiving at the Hexum's Bethany home with his dad, mom, Michelle, and two brothers, Tyler, 17, and Cade, 4.&lt;br/&gt;It's a rare day away from Randall Children's Hospital at Legacy Emanuel, where Cole has spent much of his time the past 2-1/2 months. He'll be back to the hospital Monday for more treatment.&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;He's gone through the majority of really hard stuff,&amp;quot; Brian Hexum said.&lt;br/&gt;Burkitt's is a rare and aggressive type of leukemia that requires aggressive treatment. In Cole's case, he had 90 percent of his bone marrow affected by the diseased white blood cells.&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;They were just blasting him with the highest dosage (of chemotherapy) you can,&amp;quot; Brian Hexum said. &amp;quot;It's absolutely brutal.&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;Sores in his mouth made eating impossible for awhile; he had to be fed through a tube.&lt;br/&gt;The family absorbed another shock on Nov. 9 when Brian's father, Richard Hexum — &amp;quot;Grampy Hexum&amp;quot; to the boys — died of pulmonary fibrosis in Eugene. He was 70. &amp;quot;He and Cole really bonded,&amp;quot; Brian Hexum said. &amp;quot;I wish Grampy would've been around to see Cole get through this.&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;Cole hasn't been able to attend school, much less play the sports he loves — soccer, flag football and basketball.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Cole Hexum holds the championship trophy from the &amp;quot;Cole's Bros.&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;Courtesy Hexum family&lt;br/&gt;Instead, Cole's flag football team, previously the Destroyers, changed its team name to &amp;quot;Cole's Bros.&amp;quot; Cole wasn't able to attend any of the games, but the second-graders wore messages of support for their teammate on their eye black, and then went undefeated to win their league championship. Cole got his own honorary trophy.&lt;br/&gt;Brian Hexum, an Oregon graduate and a season-ticket holder for the Ducks since 1994, has long enjoyed taking Cole to sporting events. Cole will sit patiently and intently at games, especially when watching the Ducks.&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;He doesn't get fidgety or anything,&amp;quot; Brian said. &amp;quot;He really understands what's going on.&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;When he was diagnosed in September, Cole also wanted to understand what was happening to him. Someone asked him if he was afraid.&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;No,&amp;quot; Cole said. &amp;quot;I saw my mom go through it. I can handle it, too.&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;Michelle Hexum was diagnosed with ovarian cancer on Feb. 5, 2009. Her successful fight inspired Cole, whose final treatment is scheduled for Feb. 4, 2013.&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;If Cole wasn't so strong, it would make it harder for us to handle,&amp;quot; Brian said.&lt;br/&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.oregonlive.com/runoregon/2012/11/run_for_cole_race_recap.html&quot;&gt;unexpected outpouring of support&lt;/a&gt; — from family, friends and total strangers — has made things easier for the Hexums, too. Fundraisers, donations and sales of &amp;quot;Go Team Cole&amp;quot; gear — available at the family's website, &lt;a href=&quot;http://goteamcole.com/&quot;&gt;GoTeamCole.com&lt;/a&gt; — is covering much of the estimated $500,000 in medical expenses.&lt;br/&gt;After Cole gets better, the Hexums are planning to support other sick children through additional fundraising. They've already provided gifts and encouragement for families going through a similar ordeal.&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;We've been really blessed,&amp;quot; Brian said. &amp;quot;It really restores your faith in humanity.&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;A special connection&lt;br/&gt;Will Murphy first heard about Cole's illness through his brother, Andrew, who works with a family friend of the Hexums. Soon, Murphy was posting messages of support on the Go Team Cole Facebook page, sending a Ducks poster autographed by virtually the entire team and shipping off that &amp;quot;89&amp;quot; beanie — Murphy's uniform number — that Cole now refuses to take off.&lt;br/&gt;In return, Murphy got a yellow &amp;quot;Team Cole&amp;quot; bracelet and a new friendship.&lt;br/&gt;When Murphy, a senior from Albany, scored his first UO touchdown in the Ducks' victory over Cal two weeks ago, the Hexums paused the TV while Murphy, laying on his back, held the football in the air, the yellow bracelet around his left wrist; Cole stood in front of the TV to pose for a picture.&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;I thought of Cole right away,&amp;quot; Murphy said of his touchdown.&lt;br/&gt;Murphy had extended an invitation to the Hexums to visit an Oregon practice; the plan was for Cole and the family to attend the Washington game last month, but Cole wasn't well enough to travel yet. Murphy sent a message after the game: &amp;quot;This win was for you, Cole.&amp;quot;&lt;br/&gt;Finally, doctors cleared Cole to travel to Eugene last week for the Stanford game. The day started with an unknown UO student volunteering to hold up a giant-sized sign of Cole's face in the background of ESPN's &amp;quot;College GameDay&amp;quot; show, which was being broadcast from the UO campus.&lt;br/&gt;On Monday, Cole got to meet his favorite Duck.&lt;br/&gt;&amp;quot;I was pretty pumped we finally made it happen,&amp;quot; Murphy said.&lt;br/&gt;As they left practice Monday morning, Cole riding on top of his dad's shoulders, Murphy walking and chatting next to them, it was hard to tell who enjoyed the experience more.&lt;br/&gt;-- &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:ajude@oregonian.com/&quot;&gt;Adam Jude&lt;/a&gt;; follow on &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/A_Jude&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Entries/2012/11/22_An_uplifting_visit_with_the_Oregon_Ducks_for_young_Cole_Hexum_-_and_vice_versa_files/11901891-large.png" length="300202" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Its rally time for Cole Hexum</title>
      <link>http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Entries/2012/11/21_Its_rally_time_for_Cole_Hexum.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">914adad1-b288-48c3-8369-22b862ad7d1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 09:50:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Entries/2012/11/21_Its_rally_time_for_Cole_Hexum_files/00003436267106_1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Media/object024_1.png&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:160px; height:121px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Community teams up for second-grader battling rare cancer&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;by: JAIME VALDEZ - Cole and Michelle Hexum say they plan to support others fighting cancer after the Hexums received so much support from the community. The Hexums have Christmas gifts planned for patients at Doernbecher Childrens Hospital.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;by: SUBMITTED PHOTO - Unable to play flag football, Coles teammates re-named their team Coles Bros in his honor, winning the championship trophy Nov. 11.&lt;br/&gt;When the second-graders took the field last week at Tigard High School, they weren’t just playing for the championship trophy. They were playing for their best friend.&lt;br/&gt;In September, Cole Hexum, 8, was diagnosed with Stage IV Burkitt’s leukemia — a rare, fast-growing type of leukemia that attacks the blood and bone marrow.&lt;br/&gt;The diagnosis cost Cole his hair and has made him tired. But most crushing to the energetic Bethany boy is he hasn’t been able to play soccer or flag football.&lt;br/&gt;It was a major blow to Cole, an avid sports fan who regularly balances playing on several sports teams at once.&lt;br/&gt;“He’s a Go-Go-Go kid,” his mother Michelle Hexum said.&lt;br/&gt;For the past three seasons, Cole has played on a local youth flag football team, The Destroyers.&lt;br/&gt;The team’s defensive coordinator Derek Hahm has known Cole for years on various sports teams he has coached. He said Cole’s teammates were disappointed when they heard Cole was sick and wasn’t going to be able to play with them this season.&lt;br/&gt;So they decided to do something about it.&lt;br/&gt;‘Cole’s Bros’&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;by: TIMES PHOTO: JAIME VALDEZ - Cole Hexum; his parents, Michelle and Brian; and his brothers, Cade, 4, and Tyler, 17, have received tons of support from the community as Cole fights a rare and aggressive form of leukemia.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;by: SUBMITTED PHOTO - Cole shows off the championship trophy his flag football team won in his honor on Nov. 11. Teammates wore jerseys with his name and painted messages on their faces to show their support.&lt;br/&gt;When Hahm’s son Tanner learned about his friend’s condition, Hahm said Tanner wanted to re-name the team in Cole’s honor.&lt;br/&gt;“They wanted to dedicate the season to Cole,” Hahm said. “The kids were pretty excited about dedicating it to Cole.”&lt;br/&gt;The Destroyers hung up their moniker for the season, instead adopting the name “Cole’s Bros” to show their support for their friend.&lt;br/&gt;The players wore jerseys with Cole’s name and number (No. 10) on them and wore face paint reading “Go Cole!”&lt;br/&gt;Cole’s name remained (albeit ceremoniously) on the roster, and Cole received his own jersey.&lt;br/&gt;Even teammates who didn’t know Cole got into the spirit, wearing Team Cole T-shirts and face paint, Hahm said.&lt;br/&gt;Cole wasn’t well enough to attend any of the team’s games, but that didn’t stop the Bros from going undefeated this year, winning each of their eight games in the pee-wee flag football league.&lt;br/&gt;“It was pretty fun,&amp;quot; the coach said. &amp;quot;These kids are really competitive. They’re probably the most competitive boys I know, and they didn’t want to lose. On top of that, they don’t want to lose for Cole. It was pretty intense.”&lt;br/&gt;The team played its championship game at Tigard High School on Nov. 11. Cole wasn’t well enough to attend the game, but Cole’s parents Brian and Michelle Hexum made sure to be there, cheering on the team.&lt;br/&gt;The players gave Michelle and Brian high fives on the sidelines and easily walking away with a 28-16 victory, Hahm said.&lt;br/&gt;That night, the team made sure Cole got his own trophy.&lt;br/&gt;“That was probably one of the biggest smiles I have ever seen him have,” Hahm said. “He was really proud of his buddies.”&lt;br/&gt;Community support&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;by: JAIME VALDEZ - Cole tires easily these days, his mother Michelle Hexum says. Cole is usually a 'Go-Go-Go kid.'&lt;br/&gt;Cole's Bros aren’t alone in their support of Cole.&lt;br/&gt;Several organizations have been rallying for the energetic 8-year-old over the past few months.&lt;br/&gt;In October, Athletic Republic of Tigard donated 10 percent of its proceeds to Cole, and a special soccer tournament in Cole’s honor was held last weekend in Hillsboro. This fall, an indoor soccer team is going by the name Team Cole in his honor.&lt;br/&gt;Cole was invited to the University of Oregon vs. Oregon State University Civil War football game this weekend and has gotten support from UO players who sported Team Cole insignias during a recent game.&lt;br/&gt;Proceeds from a sold-out silent auction on Dec. 1 will go to Cole’s treatment, and the Northwest Youth Sports Association is donating a portion of its proceeds from Christmas tree sales to the family.&lt;br/&gt;Michelle Hexum, herself a cancer survivor, said the show of support from the community has been staggering.&lt;br/&gt;“It is pretty amazing,” she said. “I wish I could just go out and hug every single one of them and hug them and tell them the difference that they have made for our family. It is pretty unbelievable.”&lt;br/&gt;Giving back&lt;br/&gt;The Hexums have received so much support, Brian said, that they have started Cole’s Cause, a group dedicated to helping kids battling cancer.&lt;br/&gt;“When Cole is done with this treatment, all the fundraising will go to help pay his medical bills,” his father said. “But the leftovers will go to Cole’s Cause, where he can start to help out other kids with cancer.”&lt;br/&gt;The family is already paying it forward, with plans to present gifts this week to two patients at Doernbecher Children’s Hospital.&lt;br/&gt;On Monday night, Cole was feeling good — better than he has in a long time.&lt;br/&gt;“It’s because of Thanksgiving,&amp;quot; he said. &amp;quot;I need some turkey. And some taffy.”&lt;br/&gt;But the energy is short lived. Cole spends about 80 percent of his time in the hospital getting treatment.&lt;br/&gt;Burkitt’s leukemia is a very aggressive cancer. About 90 percent of Cole’s bone marrow was affected by the cancer, Michelle Hexum said. The cancer doubles in size every few hours, but so far, Cole’s prognosis is good, she added.&lt;br/&gt;If things go according to plan, his treatment will end in February, and he’ll be able to return to school — and the football field — next year.&lt;br/&gt;“I want to play sports again about a month after I’m done (with treatment),” said Cole, bouncing as he sits on a couch at his home in Bethany. “Hopefully in the spring.”&lt;br/&gt;For more on Cole and his journey visit goteamcole.com.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.teamcole.org/teamcole/Blog/Entries/2012/11/21_Its_rally_time_for_Cole_Hexum_files/00003436267106_1.jpg" length="67075" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
